---------------------------------------

* [ ]  News
* [ ]  Pages
* [ ]  FAQ
* [ ]  About Apps
* [ ]  Links
* [ ]  SiteMap

Discover iHyperg’s apps on Google Play! From powerful photo editors to productivity tools – we’ve got what you need. [Open](https://play.google.com/store/apps/dev?id=6896025788077665075)

IHYPERG PRIVACY POLICY
======================

Effective date: August 8, 2019

ihyperg ("us", "we", or "our") operates the "ihyperg console" (the "Service").

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.

We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions.

---

Information Collection And Use
------------------------------

### We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

### Types of Data Collected:

Personal Data

While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

* Cookies and Usage Data ( This data is collected on the website )
    
* Data collected by Google Admob/Adsense to display recommended ads ( This data is collected in applications and website, To find out what data Google Admob collects, you can find out on the website: [apps.admob.com](http://apps.admob.com/) )

Usage Data

We may also collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit our Service or when you access the Service by or through a mobile device ("Usage Data").

This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

When you access the Service by or through a mobile device, this Usage Data may include information such as the type of mobile device you use, your mobile device unique ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browser you use, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

Tracking & Cookies Data

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:

* Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service. (Example: The site remembers which theme you use on the site)
    
* Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
    
* Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

Use of Data

ihyperg uses the collected data for various purposes: 

* To provide and maintain the Service
    
* To notify you about changes to our Service
    
* To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
    
* To provide customer care and support
    
* To provide analysis or valuable information so that we can improve the Service
    
* To monitor the usage of the Service
    
* To detect, prevent and address technical issues

Transfer Of Data

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

ihyperg will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

Disclosure Of Data

Legal Requirements

ihyperg may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

* To comply with a legal obligation
    
* To protect and defend the rights or property of ihyperg 
    
* To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
    
* To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
    
* To protect against legal liability

Security Of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

Analytics

We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

* Google Analytics: Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: [https://policies.google.com/privacy](https://policies.google.com/privacy)

Links To Other Sites

Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.

We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.

Children's Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Children has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.

You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:

By email: [hyperghelp@gmail.com](mailto:hyperghelp@gmail.com)

© 2019-2024 IHYPERG.COM - All Rights Reserved.

Did someone say … cookies?
--------------------------

IHYPERG uses cookies to make your experience better and brighter! By accepting, you’ll help us remember your preferences, like your favorite theme, and keep everything running smoothly. Enjoy your time here!

Accept cookies
